http://www.buyonlinenow.com/privacy-security.asp

Home > Privacy & Security Policy
Your Privacy
BuyOnlineNow.com respects and protects your privacy. We will never provide your personal information to any outside organization, except as required by law.
1. What does BuyOnlineNow.com's privacy policy cover?
This privacy policy applies to our web site and to our use and storage of customer data.
2. What information does BuyOnlineNow.com collect and how is it used?
We use cookies to improve the ease of your shopping experience with us. This cookie file (placed on your computer by your browser) allows you to easily access your customer information each and every visit. We do not and cannot use this cookie to collect information about you or your computer. We collect only information knowingly provided by you. We collect your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number and company name during registration. We also collect your credit card number when you complete an order. To further protect your security, we do not store your credit card number on our servers, therefore you are required to reenter it each time you purchase from us. During order checkout, we also record your PC's IP address (it's digital Internet Protocol address).
We do provide the details required to complete your order to the company contracted by BuyOnlineNow.com to provide inventory and order fulfillment. Your credit card transactions are processed on our web site by CyberSource and information required to complete payments & credits is provided to CyberSource during processing. This information is provided only as necessary to deliver your orders and is not used by the fulfillment company for any other purpose. We do monitor our website's traffic and usage patterns. This non-personal information, containing no individual identifiers, may be provided to 3rd parties for BuyOnlineNow.com's business or marketing purposes.
BuyOnlineNow uses Google Display Advertising to help increase user web experience by using 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests). BuyOnlineNow and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to your site.
BuyOnlineNow also uses Google Remarketing to advertise online. BuyOnlineNow and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to your website. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show BuyOnlineNow ads on sites across the Internet.
You may opt-out of these Google services at anytime by using the Google Ads Settings or the opt-out browser add-on.
3. What are cookies and how are they used?
We use cookies to improve the ease of your shopping experience with us. This cookie file (placed on your computer by your browser) allows you to easily access your customer information each and every visit. We do not and cannot use this cookie to collect information about you or your computer. While you are welcome to shop You will need to accept cookies to complete an order at BuyOnlineNow.com.
4. Does BuyOnlineNow.com share customer information?
We do not share your personal information with any outside organizations, except as required by law.
5. How does BuyOnlineNow.com protect this information?
BuyOnlineNow.com uses a secure server that encrypts your personal information before it is sent to us. This encryption makes it impossible for any unauthorized party to read any information you send to us. We also encrypt all records stored on our servers and physical access to our data center is protected. Access to our servers requires individual authorization and identification.
6. Correction or deletion of customer information
You may change your customer record on our website by visiting our My Account. To request removal of your customer information from our database, please email us at
. We will email confirmation once your customer record has been removed from our database. Details of orders completed for you cannot be removed and will be retained in our database.
7. Promotional Emails
We will send you promotional e-mails periodically featuring current specials, coupons and deals. You may "opt-out" or unsubscribe from our promotional emails at anytime by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email that was received. Also your privacy is very important to us and we will never give your email address to third party vendors.
Your Security
All information submitted to BuyOnlineNow.com is done using SSL (secure socket layer) 128 bit encryption certified by Verisign, an Internet leader in secure transactions. Our web site is a Verisign Secure Site, you can view Verisign's verification of this security here. SSL encodes all information sent between you and BuyOnlineNow.com and renders it unreadable to any 3rd party. SSL encryption is supported by Netscape Navigator 3.X and higher and also by Microsoft Explorer 3.01 or higher. For your protection, we do not store your credit card information on our servers. This information, once used to complete your order, is removed from our database. You will need to enter your credit card information each time you place an order, ensuring that no one will be able to complete an unauthorized purchase with your credit card account information.
What Our Customers are Saying...
Customer Service ~ Jacqueline from Eglin AFB Fl
You are awesome! ~ Thomas from Detroit, MI
You guys are Awesome!! ~ Floyd from Youngsville, NC
Enter to Win a Fellowes Laminator!
Sign up now to receive valuable deals, coupons and promotions and be entered to win!
Help?
Copyright © 2020 BuyOnlineNow. All Rights Reserved.
Log In
Create Account
Contact Us
Help?
